the amanda seals show hey y'all it's the amanda seal show i'm amanda seals it's time to get into
some pop culture news now i'm not sure if y'all saw the grammys uh i did not watch the whole show
because i had other things that i decided to do at that time however thanks to the internet we
saw clips we saw clips so let's talk about this one right here when jay-z pulled out the full clip
on the audience i don't want to embarrass this young lady but she has more grammys than everyone
and never won album in a year so even by your own metrics that doesn't work cough up a lung
where i'm from marcy's son ain't nothing nice first of all let's ask the question was it wrong
for jay-z to use this time while he was getting an award to criticize the grammys do we feel like
that in itself was sideways nah not at all that's what hip-hop does at the grammys it's notorious so
yeah word we'll take his foot of children yes yes yes do he does he should he get credit
for advocating for beyonce especially in front of his daughter blue ivy who had joined him on stage
as a married man i'm gonna say hell yeah i feel like at the end of the day it doesn't matter what
anybody in the grammys thought if that impressed his wife who he has to go home to then you know what
it's a win